Discover the mystery that connects them all.
2 Hearts is a romance, drama film directed by Lance Hool.
When illness strikes two people who are polar opposites, life
and death bring them together in surprising ways.
Chris, played by Jacob Elordi.
Jorge, played by Adan Canto.
Sam, played by Tiera Skovbye.
Leslie, played by Radha Mitchell.
Grace, played by Kari Matchett.
Eric, played by Tahmoh Penikett.
2 Hearts is a 2020 American romantic drama film directed by Lance Hool and
starring Jacob Elordi, Adan Canto, Tiera Skovbye and Radha Mitchell.
It marks Hool's first directorial movie credit since 1999.
It is based on the true story of Leslie and Jorge
Bacardi and Christopher Gregory.
The film was theatrically released in the United States on October 16,
2020, receiving generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of faith, disease, organ transplant, destiny.
The tone is emotional.